

# **Profile**

Passionate and experienced media guy goes IT. Bringing forth 10+ years experience of communication, planning and coordination skills gained on editors and directors positions. Wholly focused on final task success. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

# **Project Experience**

<u>Portfolio.</u> This is a simple landing with a minimalist responsive design based on vanilla JS and pure CSS. Visit to get to know me better;)

<u>Filmoteka/Movie-API</u>. <u>Link</u>. Technologies: REST APIs, JS, HTML/SASS, Handlebars, Firebase. A webpage with a responsive layout based on vanilla JS and themoviedb-api. Includes color switcher and personal library.

<u>Kapusta: smart finance</u>. Link to <u>front/back</u>. A multipage app for managing your savings and expences. Helps you to keep track of your income and spendings. Team-lead and developer role. Technologies: React, Redux, MongoDB, Node.js, Google authentication, Swagger.

<u>Chat app: Link.</u> A responsive React messaging app based on socket.io with authentication, individual/group chat functionality, chat editing, notification ect. Technologies: React, Node.js, Socket.io, MongoDB, Firebase.

# **Employment History**

Filmmaker / Director, Screen Media, Kyiv from march 2015 to october 2022

Script-writing, coordinating filming crew, making short and non-fiction movies. Author of documentaries: Chaplains (2015), Those Who Are Faithfull (2017), Man of Will (2021).

Editor, zhyve.tv / Equalympic, Kyiv from march 2014 to january 2022

Development of program ideas, plots, videos. Writing story scripts and programs, working with the presenter and operators on the set. Supervising journalist.

### Education

FullStack Developer, GoIT from august 2021 to september 2022

Master of History and Law, Kherson State University, Kherson from march 2006 to september 2011

Master of Communication, Ukrainian Catholic University, Lviv from september 2011 to june 2013

### **Details**

380958933653

baggins999@gmail.com

LinkedIN

GitHub

#### Technical skills

HTML5/CSS3/SASS

**JavaScript** 

**TypeScript** 

React

Redux

Node.js

WebPack

**REST APIs** 

MongoDB

Socket.io

### **Soft Skills**

Communication and interpersonal

skills

Self-awareness

Emotional intelligence

Teamwork

Critical thinking

#### Languages

English - Advanced

Ukrainian - Native

Russian - Fluent